const decks = [
  {
    id: 1,
    title: "decktitle1",
    cards: [
      {
        question: "question1",
        answer: "answer1",
      },
      {
        question: "question2",
        answer: "answer2",
      },
      {
        question: "question3",
        answer: "answer3",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    title: "decktitle2",
    cards: [
      {
        question: "question1",
        answer: "answer1",
      },
      {
        question: "question2",
        answer: "answer2",
      },
      {
        question: "question3",
        answer: "answer3",
      },
    ],
  },
];

export default decks;

/////got errors here, deck1, deck2 undefined
// const data = [
//     deck1 : {
//       id: 1,
//       title: "decktitle",
//       cards: [
//         {
//           question: "question1",
//           answer: "answer1",
//         },
//         {
//           question: "question2",
//           answer: "answer2",
//         },
//         {
//           question: "question3",
//           answer: "answer3",
//         },
//     ],
//     },

//     deck2: {
//       id: 2,
//       title: "decktitle2",
//       cards: [
//         {
//           question: "question1",
//           answer: "answer1",
//         },
//         {
//           question: "question2",
//           answer: "answer2",
//         },
//         {
//           question: "question3",
//           answer: "answer3",
//         },
//       ],
//     },
//   ];
